socializr.com 2010-12-30

# Socializr - Privacy Policy

Socializr does not send Spam or sell email addresses. Our users control the information they enter into Socializr, and may modify or remove this information, cancel their account, or block future communications from Socializr, at any time. 

Socializr is a free web service for sharing event and party information with your friends. To accomplish this, each Socializr Member creates his or her own profile, chooses friends to automatically share events with, creates public or private events, invites people to events, and RSVPs to events of their choosing. The following policy explains our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

Information Collected 

1\. Your Personally Identifiable Information Collected by Socializr: 

When you register with the Socializr service, our registration form may require you to give us certain information such as your name, email address, and zip code. Socializr will also collect other information you volunteer to us through use of our service. We refer to this information as "Personally Identifiable Information." You may always choose not to provide such Personally Identifiable Information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service or particular content. We may also collect demographic and other data, which may include Personally Identifiable Information, generally through surveys and forms which you may or may not choose to participate in. If you place an order for goods or services through Socializr, you may be required to enter your credit card number and information, as well as your shipping address and/or other contact information. 

2\. Profile Page: 

If you choose to sign up for a free Socializr account, you will have a Profile page on the site, containing your name and some basic demographic information. You may also add additional optional information to your Profile. You may control what type of Profile information is shown to others through your Privacy Preferences in your Account Settings. Links to your Profile Page will be included on other Socializr pages such as event pages, which may include links to Profile pages from the guest list entries. If you send a message to a Socializr user through Socializr's internal Messages feature, that person will be informed of your email address. PLEASE NOTE THAT, REGARDLESS OF WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION A MEMBER CHOOSES TO INCLUDE IN HIS OR HER PROFILE, OR WHAT PRIVACY PREFERENCES HE OR SHE CHOOSES, CERTAIN INFORMATION ABOUT EACH MEMBER WILL BE INCLUDED IN THAT MEMBER'S PUBLIC PROFILE AND WILL BE ACCESSIBLE TO ANYONE VISITING THAT PROFILE PAGE ON THE SOCIALIZR WEBSITE. 

3\. Your Personally Identifiable Information Collected by Socializr's Business Partners: 

Socializr works with third-party advertising companies, sponsors and other companies with whom we do business ("Business Partners") to place advertising on our site and in email communications sent to our registered users and to recipients of invitations, Reminders, and other communications related to the Socializr service. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, may be used to serve advertising to you on this site. 

Socializr may correlate or match registered Users' information, including Personally Identifiable Information, with information held by our Business Partners to target ads or otherwise improve the effectiveness of our service. Our Business Partners may read or set cookies on your hard drive, use pixel tags, track which ads you have viewed, or collect other information about you. 

From time to time, Socializr may also have special offers or promotions that are sponsored by a Business Partner. In order to participate in these offers, you may be required to follow a separate registration process. If you consent to receive information from a Business Partner, through an opt-in or opt-out process, Socializr may pass your information to such Business Partner. 

Socializr may also offer goods or services for purchase available by our Business Partners. If you purchase goods or services offered through Socializr by a Business Partner, then you may be required to submit Personally Identifiable Information in order to complete the transaction and Socializr may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to such Business Partner for that purpose. 

In some cases, we may enter into a promotional relationship with a Business Partner in which we prominently display their brand name or trademarks on pages that appear the same as or very similar to the pages of the Socializr service. These pages are known as "Co-Branded Pages" and these particular Business Partners are known as "Co-Branded Business Partners." If the page on which you submit information is a Co-Branded Page, or was accessed by clicking on a link on a Co-Branded Page, then we may share your personal information with the associated Co-Branded Business Partner. Co-Branded Business Partners may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. Socializr disclaims all liability for the privacy policies and procedures on any Business Partner or Co-Branded Business Partner Web site. You will need to contact the Co-Branded Business Partner to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. Additionally, you agree that we may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such Co-Branded Business Partners in the same manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information you submit to us (see Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information by Business Partners below). 

4\. Guest Contact Information: 

In order to send messages to your guests through the Socializr service, we require that you submit to Socializr current, valid email addresses for your guests. When you send messages to your guests through our service (e.g., a Socializr invitation or a Reminder), we collect and retain the email addresses or other pertinent contact information of those persons to whom you send the message. Except as described below in the Section titled "When We May Disclose Your Personally Identifiable Information, Data or Guest Contact Information", we do not sell, share or otherwise provide the guest contact information you submit to Socializr to any third party. 

5\. Cookies: Socializr wants to optimize your experience by ensuring that the most relevant information, promotions and offers are displayed to you while using the Socializr web site. A common manner in which to do this is by placing cookies on your computer. Cookies are strings of text and numbers that can identify your computer to us when you visit our site, and which may be correlated with your Personally Identifiable Information in our log files. In the event a location, like a zip code, is not available in your profile or you have not searched in a location on Socializr, we will cookie your location from your last Socializr invitation. 

6\. IP Address: When you visit our site, we log standard information such as your IP address, which is a number that can be used to identify your location and Internet Service Provider, along with the URL from which you came to our site and the URLs visited on our site. A URL is the full address of a Web site page, which may or may not contain some Personally Identifiable Information about the person who is viewing it. 

When we send messages to you or others, we may provide a URL link to the Socializr site that contains an alphanumeric identifier, which allows us to identify the person to whom we sent the message so that we can personalize our content for that individual. 

7\. Pixel Tags: Socializr may use pixel tags to gather information about the emails we send to our registered users and to recipients of messages. Pixel tags are tiny graphic files, not visible to the human eye, that are included in our HTML-encoded email messages. When such a message is opened in an HTML-capable email program, the recipient's computer will access our server to retrieve the pixel tag file, allowing us to record and store, along with your email address, the date and time the recipient viewed the invite or reminder, that the recipient's email program is capable of receiving HTML-encoded email, and other standard logging information. The pixel tag also may see or read cookies. For more information about cookies and how to disable their use, see the section below on "Use of Cookies." 

Use of Information 

1\. Use Of Your Personally Identifiable Information by Socializr: 

Socializr does not sell, share or otherwise provide any "Personally Identifiable Information" you give to us with any Business Partner without your consent, which may be obtained through an opt-in or opt-out request (see Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information by Business Partners below), unless required by law, court order or as required to technically operate the service, or to complete a transaction or order. Socializr does reserve the right to share your Personally Identifiable Information with its parent, subsidiary or affiliated entities ("affiliated entities" are those companies owned or controlled by Socializr's parent company). We use the collected Personally Identifiable Information to schedule events for you, to contact the recipients on your Socializr list, to contact you in connection with your transactions, posting and other activities on the site, to forward to you messages from other Users, to communicate with you about events or activities in your area and to operate the Socializr service. These types of communications may contain commercial messages, such as banner ads and special offers. You may control the types of communications your receive from us via your Notification Preferences. In addition, we use your Personally Identifiable Information to help us provide you with personalized content, advertising, and commercial messages (collectively, "Content"). 

2\. Use Of Your Personally Identifiable Information By Other Users: 

Users and/or guests invited to the same events as you will be able to view your name on the guest list, which will also link to your Profile Page. In addition, other Users may choose to email you. However, to ensure your privacy, Socializr will not display or give out your email address or any other contact information to other users, unless you send a message or invitation to that user, you are on the guestlist of an event hosted by that user, or that user already has your email address. If you send a message to a Socializr user through Socializr's internal Messages feature, that person will be informed of your email address. Your contact information, including email address, will be available to the host of the event, unless you block this via your Privacy Preferences in your Account Settings. 

3\. Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information by Socializr's Business Partners: 

In order to provide offers of particular interest to you, Socializr may share demographic, geographic, and other Personally Identifiable Information with its Business Partners with your consent. 

PLEASE NOTE: The privacy practices of advertisers and other companies who provide services or advertising through our site are not covered by this privacy policy. Please contact those companies directly for more information about their privacy practices. If you wish to prevent those companies from setting cookies on your browser, you may set your browser to refuse cookies or to warn you before setting a cookie. Disabling cookies set by companies whose products or services are advertised on this site should not affect your ability to use this site. 

4\. Use Of Guest Contact Information: 

We use your guests' contact information to allow them to respond to and comment on your Socializr invitation. We may send Reminders to your guests and display their email addresses to your other guests. We also may send a post-event email to you and your guests. If you use our Reminders service, we use the information you provide in your Reminders to send it to you. Socializr does not sell, share or otherwise provide any guests' contact information you give to us with any Business Partner, unless required by law, court order or as required to technically operate the service. 

You may delete your email address from the guest list by requesting to be removed from the guest list on the event page. Once your email address is removed from the guest list, it will no longer be accessible to other guests (unless you are subsequently invited to another party, in which case your email address will be accessible to guests of the new event). 

5\. Use Of Cookies: 

We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, among other purposes. You can always choose not to accept cookies through your browser's preference options, but you may not be able to use some of our services if you do not accept cookies. 

As described in more detail above, Business Partners display ads through our service. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our Business Partners, and we do not have access to this information. Likewise, some of our Business Partners may use cookies. We do not control their use of cookies nor have access to the information contained in or related to those cookies. Please contact our Business Partners directly for more information about their privacy practices. 

6\. Use Of IP Addresses: 

We use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site and otherwise provide our service to you. IP addresses may be disclosed to Business Partners if Socializr believes in good faith that the law or legal process requires it, or to protect the rights or property of Socializr or others. In addition, our Business Partners may use information derived from your IP address, such as conducting a reverse domain name lookup, in order to provide advertisements more tailored to your interests. 

When We May Disclose Your Personally Identifiable Information, Socializr Invitation Content, Data or Guest Contact Information 

Socializr may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, the contents of your private communications, or the contact information of your guests if required to do so by law or court order. Your Personally Identifiable Information may also be disclosed if necessary in order to complete a transaction such as the fulfillment of an order or purchase placed by you. Socializr will in no way disclose the contents of your Socializr invitations other than to the intended recipient(s) unless required (1) by law or court order, (2) to protect Socializr's rights and property, (3) to protect against unauthorized use of the Socializr site, and (4) during emergencies such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk. Also, certain technical processing of email messages and their content may be required to: (1) send and receive messages; (2) conform to connecting networks' technical requirements; (3) conform to the limitations of the Service; or (4) conform to other similar requirements. 

It is possible that as we continue to develop our Web site and our business, Socializr and/or related assets might be acquired. In such a transaction, customer information may be transferred to the acquiring entity. 

Security 

This site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and integrity of the information under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected by the Socializr service in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security. Socializr is a free web service for sharing event and party information with your friends. We do not use SSL to encrypt information you send and receive to and from our website. Do not store highly sensitive information like medical or financial information at Socializr. 

Other Web Sites; Links 

This Web site contains links to other Web sites. Socializr is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Opt-Out/Correct/Delete/Deactivate 

At any time, you may edit or remove the information on your Profile Page, cancel your account, or block future communications from Socializr, via your My Account page or links at the bottom of communications sent by Socializr. 

Changes to this Policy 

Socializr reserves the right to amend this privacy policy at its sole discretion. If we make any substantive changes to the policy in the future with regard to how we use your information, we will notify registered users who have agreed to receive the Socializr newsletter through that newsletter. For those users who have not agreed to accept the newsletter, substantive changes will be posted on the site in this location, and the date of the changes will be noted on the Web site for a period of time. Your continued use of the site after the changes are posted constitutes your agreement to the changes with regard to information collected in the past and in the future from you. If you do not agree to the changes, you may opt-out as described above. 

Contacting the Web Site 

We strive to do everything we can to protect the privacy of our users. Please feel free to share any comments and concerns with us. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

Socializr, Inc., 660 4th Street, Suite 240, San Francisco, California 94107 

LAST REVISED ON: April 28, 2007
